ubiquityservers.com 2016-05-08

# Privacy Policy - Ubiquity Hosting

**Ubiquity Hosting Solutions has a long-standing policy of protecting customer privacy.**

We believe that you should know what information we collect from you, as well as how that information is used, disclosed, and protected. We have created this policy statement (the "Policy") to explain our privacy practices and policies. 

We will not sell or disclose your personal information to unaffiliated third parties without your consent except as otherwise provided in this Policy or our Terms of Service and Appropriate Use Policy. We may use information about who you are, where and when you browse on the Web, where your wireless device is located, and how you use our network to provide you better service and enrich your user experience when you sign up or use any of our products or services. 

Ubiquity Hosting Solutions may make available shorter or machine-readable versions of this Privacy Policy. These additional policies are intended only as summaries of this complete Privacy Policy. This Policy applies to customers who purchase and use our services and products in the United States. Collection, use, disclosure, and protection of personal information may be subject to different regulation outside the United States. 

Ubiquity Hosting Solutions will revise and update this Policy as it is deemed appropriate, including, for example, if our practices change or if changes in the law so require. You should refer back to this page for the latest information.
